<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-04-19T17:12:57+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Keshav’s Blog</title><subtitle>A short description of your site's purpose</subtitle><entry><title type="html">About</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/About/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="About" /><published>2020-04-19T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-04-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/About</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/About/">&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: justify&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I currently work as a Software Development Engineer in the Autonomous Robots Research Team (Smart Devices) at CTO, Wipro Limited. I am currently involved in the design and development of scalable and configurable robotic software modules. I primarily code in Python and mostly work with the Robot Operating System (ROS) and supporting software including Gazebo, Moveit! and RViz. I also design robot simulation environments to aid software development and testing. Click Here to Download my Resume&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I graduated with a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science and Technology from Vellore Institute of Technology in 2018. During this period, I had designed and developed a few robot prototypes including an AI powered Chessboard. I have worked in several projects in the fields of Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning and Game Theory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other than computer science I am also passionate about performing magic and being involved in films.I directed one short film and have worked as the script writer in many individual projects. I have also worked as a VFX/Graphics Designer and am proficient in skills involving video editing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I currently work as a Software Development Engineer in the Autonomous Robots Research Team (Smart Devices) at CTO, Wipro Limited. I am currently involved in the design and development of scalable and configurable robotic software modules. I primarily code in Python and mostly work with the Robot Operating System (ROS) and supporting software including Gazebo, Moveit! and RViz. I also design robot simulation environments to aid software development and testing. Click Here to Download my Resume</summary></entry></feed>